Meghan Brown

Account Executive/Customer Service

Cypress, CA 90630

meghanstephan4_25u@indeedemail.com - 562-822-6795

High level experienced Account Executive focused in Customer Service with 14 years of corporate selling. Success in exceeding quotas, skilled in handling challenging accounts, cross selling, add-on services, and delivering solutions.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

SALES COORDINATOR/EXECUTIVE ASSISTANT

JANUS WORLDWIDE - 2016-01 - 2016-10

Identify and qualify potential sales leads for upcoming trade shows and other events Successfully pursued new customers through outbound email campaigns and calling strategies Build and cultivate relationships with potential sales leads

INSIDE SALES REPRESENTATIVE

MCNICHOLS COMPANY - 2012-02 - 2014-10

Established close client relationships and developed a loyal customer base by providing excellent continuous sales and technical customer support

- Consistently achieved sales goals each quarter through leadership, planning, and effective implementation
- Identified product selections and assisted customers in making product selections based on customer's needs and product specifications

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE

RPM CONSOLIDATED SERVICES - 2011-10 - 2012-02

Drove new business growth and increased volume of current accounts by contacting new and existing customers to discuss their needs and to explain how those needs could be met by specific products and services

- Provided superior customer support through knowledge and understanding of available services as well as ability to problem solve quickly
- Prepared timely and accurate proposals on project bids, providing detailed follow up to educate customers

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE

UNISHIPPERS INC - 2009-10 - 2011-10

Developed successful sales relationships with CEO's, Owners, and Directors by phone and in person through effectively identifying needs and providing solutions

- Exceeded margin quotas for each sales period
- Recommended products based on customers' needs and interests and answered customers' sales or technical questions

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Marketing

University of Phoenix

2013-12

SKILLS

Microsoft Office, CRM

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Driven self-starter

Excellent communicator

Strong relationship builder

Responsible

Skilled problem solver and critical thinker

Collaborative team leader

Proficient in Microsoft Office, CRM